University of Connecticut, Provost's Office Records 1989.0003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV: Schools and Colleges, 1948-1971
  - Subseries C: 1968-1969
    - Engineering, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1090)
      - Engineering Experiment Station (Box 28:, Folder 1096)
      - Mechanical Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1097)
      - Metallurgy, Department of (Box 28:, Folder 1098)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1099)
      - Architecture (Box 28:, Folder 1100)
      - Art (Box 28:, Folder 1101)
      - Art Museum (Box 28:, Folder 1102)
      - Music (Box 28:, Folder 1103)
      - Theatre (Box 28:, Folder 1104)
    - Graduate School (Box 28:, Folder 1105)
      - Research Foundation (Box 28:, Folder 1106)
      - Research Foundation, Connecticut (Box 28:, Folder 1107)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1108-1109)
      - Child Development and Family Relations (Box 28:, Folder 1110)
      - Clothing, Textiles and Related Art (Box 28:, Folder 1111)
      - Foods and Nutrition (Box 28:, Folder 1112)
    - Law, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1113)
      - Educational Policy Committee (Box 28:, Folder 1114)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1115)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1116)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1117)
    - Physical Education, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1118)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 28:, Folder 1119)
      - Physical Education: Search Committee for Director (Box 28:, Folder 1120)
    - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1121)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1122)
  - Subseries D: 1969-1971
    - Agriculture, School of (Box 29:, Folder 1123-1127)
      - Agricultural Economics (Box 29:, Folder 1128)
      - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 29:, Folder 1129)
      - Agricultural Extension (Box 29:, Folder 1130-1131)
      - Animal Disease (Box 29:, Folder 1132)
      - Animal Genetics (Box 29:, Folder 1133)
      - Animal Industries (Box 29:, Folder 1134)
      - Nutritional Science Department (Box 29:, Folder 1135)
      - Plant Science (Box 29:, Folder 1136)
      - Ratcliffe Hicks (Box 29:, Folder 1137)
      - Rural Sociology (Box 29:, Folder 1138)
    - Allied Health, School of (Box 29:, Folder 1139)
      - Allied Health Professions (Box 29:, Folder 1140-1141)
      - Allied Health Professions: Basic Improvement Grant (Box 29:, Folder 1142)
      - Allied Health: TV's (Box 29:, Folder 1143)
      - Medical Technology (Box 29:, Folder 1144)
      - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 29:, Folder 1145)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 29:, Folder 1146-1148)
      - Anthropology (Box 29:, Folder 1149)
      - Biobehavioral Sciences (Box 29:, Folder 1150)
      - Biochemistry (Box 29:, Folder 1151)
      - Biological Science Group (Box 29:, Folder 1152-1153)
      - Chemistry (Box 30:, Folder 1154)
      - Economics (Box 30:, Folder 1155)
      - English (Box 30:, Folder 1156)
      - France, Junior Year in (Box 30:, Folder 1157)
      - Geology (Box 30:, Folder 1158)
      - Germanic and Slavic Languages (Box 30:, Folder 1159)
      - History (Box 30:, Folder 1160)
      - Journalism (Box 30:, Folder 1161)
      - Linguistics (Box 30:, Folder 1162)
      - Marine Research Laboratory (Box 30:, Folder 1163)
      - Mathematics (Box 30:, Folder 1164)
      - Microbiology (Box 30:, Folder 1165)
      - National Defense (Box 30:, Folder 1166-1167)
      - Philosophy (Box 30:, Folder 1168)
      - Physics (Box 30:, Folder 1169)
      - Political Science (Box 30:, Folder 1170)
      - Psychology (Box 30:, Folder 1171)
      - Romance and Classical Languages (Box 30:, Folder 1172)
      - Sociology (Box 30:, Folder 1173)
      - Speech and Drama (Box 30:, Folder 1174)
      - Statistics (Box 30:, Folder 1175)
      - Systems and Environment (Box 30:, Folder 1176)
      - Zoology (Box 30:, Folder 1177)
    - Business Administration (Box 30:, Folder 1178)
      - Accounting (Box 30:, Folder 1179)
      - Finance (Box 30:, Folder 1180)
      - Industrial Administration (Box 30:, Folder 1181)
      - Insurance (Box 30:, Folder 1182)
      - Marketing (Box 30:, Folder 1183)
      - MBA Program (Box 31:, Folder 1184)
      - MBA Program - Mr. Orr's Correspondence (Box 31:, Folder 1185)
      - NERAC (Box 31:, Folder 1186-1187)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1188)
    - Education, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1189)
      - Audio-Visual Aids (Box 31:, Folder 1190)
      - Co-op Program For Superior Students (Box 31:, Folder 1191)
      - Educational Research (Box 31:, Folder 1192)
      - Physical Education, Department of (Box 31:, Folder 1193)
      - Radio and TV Center (Box 31:, Folder 1194-1195)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1196)
      - Aerospace Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1197)
      - Chemical Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1198)
      - Civil Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1199)
      - Electrical Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1200)
      - Mechanical Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1201)
      - Metallurgy, Department of> (Box 31:, Folder 1202)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1203)
      - Art (Box 31:, Folder 1204)
      - Art Museum (Box 31:, Folder 1205)
      - Dramatic Arts (Box 31:, Folder 1206)
      - Music (Box 31:, Folder 1207)
      - Von der Mehden (Box 31:, Folder 1208)
    - Graduate School (Box 32:, Folder 1209-1216)
      - Research Foundation (Box 32:, Folder 1217-1222)
    - Health Center (Box 32:, Folder 1223-1224)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 32:, Folder 1225)
      - Child Development and Family Relations (Box 32:, Folder 1226)
      - Clothing and Textiles (Box 32:, Folder 1227)
      - Food and Nutrition (Box 32:, Folder 1228)
    - Law, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1229-1234)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1235-1237)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1238-1241)
    - Physical Education, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1242)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 33:, Folder 1243-1244)
      - Yankee Conference (Box 33:, Folder 1245)
    - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1246)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1247-1251)
- Series V: Committees, 1968-1972
  - Accident Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1252)
  - Admissions (Box 34:, Folder 1253)
  - Animal Care Committee, Laboratory (Box 34:, Folder 1254)
  - Athletics Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1255)
  - Athletic Planning Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1256)
  - Auditorium and Little Theatre Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1257)
  - Branch Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1258)
  - Commerce Research Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1259)
  - Commencement Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1260)
  - Committee on Committees (Box 34:, Folder 1261)
  - Computer Center Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1262)
  - Conferences and Institutes (Box 34:, Folder 1263)
  - Cost of Instruction, Committee on (Box 34:, Folder 1264)
  - Continuing Education Services (Box 34:, Folder 1265)
  - Copyright Policies (Box 34:, Folder 1266)
  - Council of Deans (Box 34:, Folder 1267)
  - Council of Department Heads (Box 34:, Folder 1268)
  - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 34:, Folder 1269)
  - Council of Instruction of International and Intercultural Studies (Box 34:, Folder 1270)
  - Council on Instruction (Box 34:, Folder 1271)
  - Counseling (Box 34:, Folder 1272)
  - Diamond Jubilee Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1273)
  - Drug Abuse, Committee on (Box 34:, Folder 1274)
  - Electron Microscopy Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1275)
  - Exhibits, University Committee on (Box 34:, Folder 1276)
  - Faculty Standards (Box 34:, Folder 1277)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1278)
  - Finance Committee (Board of Trustees) (Box 34:, Folder 1279-1280)
  - Financial Assistant Policy Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1281)
  - Five, Committee of (Box 34:, Folder 1282)
  - General Scholastic Standards (Box 34:, Folder 1283)
  - Geographic Information System and Related Topics Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1284)
  - Governance, Committee on University (Box 34:, Folder 1285)
  - Graduate Admissions Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1286)
  - Graduate School Executive Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1287-1289)
  - Graduate School Executive Committee meetings (Box 34:, Folder 1290)
  - Guidelines, Committee on (Box 34:, Folder 1291)
  - Handicapped, Advisory Committee on (Box 34:, Folder 1292)
  - Health Center Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1293)
  - Health Service Advisory Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1294)
  - Honors Committee, Standing (Box 34:, Folder 1295)
  - Housing Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1296)
  - Humans in Research, Use of (Box 34:, Folder 1297)
  - Innovations (Box 34A, Folder 1298)
  - Innovative Studies Committee (Box 34A, Folder 1299)
  - Institute of Cellular Biology Executive Committee (Box 34A, Folder 1300)
  - Institute of Nutrition and Food Science Executive Committee (Box 34A, Folder 1301-1302)
  - Italian Studies Executive Committee, Center for (Box 34A, Folder 1303)
  - Joint Highway Research Council (Box 34A, Folder 1304)
  - Laboratory Safety Committee (Box 34A, Folder 1305)
  - Labor Education Center (Box 34A, Folder 1306)
  - Liaison Committee of the University and State Colleges (Box 34A, Folder 1307-1309)
  - Liaison Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1310-1315)
  - Library Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1316)
  - Long-Range Financial Planning Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1317-1318)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1319)
  - Mass Spectrometer, Advisory Committee on (Box 35:, Folder 1320)
  - Material Science Institute Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1321)
  - Naming of Buildings Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1322)
  - National Defense Training Advisory Committee, Division of (Box 35:, Folder 1323)
  - Natural Areas Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1324)
  - Office of Education: Bureau of Higher Education (Box 35:, Folder 1325)
  - Parking Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1326)
  - Pre-Law Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1327)
  - Pre-medical/Pre-dental Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1328)
  - President's Council (Box 35:, Folder 1329)
  - Provost's Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1330)
  - Provost's Search Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1331)
  - Publications Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1332)
  - Public Internship Fellowship Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1333)
  - Radio-TV Advisory Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1334)
  - Religion, Committee on (Box 35:, Folder 1335)
  - Research Council (Box 35:, Folder 1336)
  - Research Council: Faculty (Box 35:, Folder 1337)
  - Scholastic Requirement Committee: general (Box 35:, Folder 1338)
  - Scholastic Standards Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1339-1342)
  - Scholastic Standards Committee: general (Box 35A, Folder 1343)
  - Security Force (Box 35A, Folder 1344)
  - Senate Committee on Growth and Development (Box 35A, Folder 1345)
  - Senate Subcommittee: branch (Box 35A, Folder 1346)
  - Senate Subcommittee: Growth and Development (Box 35A, Folder 1347)
  - Social Science Data Center Advisory Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1348)
  - Student Advisory Committee: summer program (Box 35A, Folder 1349)
  - Student University Relations Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1350-1351)
  - Summer Sessions and Credit Extension Advisory Committee, Division of (Box 35A, Folder 1352)
  - Trustee Administrative Faculty Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1353)
  - University Extension Study Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1354)
  - University Planning, Committee of (Box 35A, Folder 1355)
  - Urban Research Advisory Committee, Institute of (Box 35A, Folder 1356)
  - Urban Semester Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1357)
  - Water Resources, Executive Committee (Box 35A, Folder 1358)
- Series VII: Faculty, 1942-1973
  - Faculty Minutes of Schools and Colleges (Box 48)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 48:, Folder 2213-2217)
    - Allied Health Professions, School of (Box 48:, Folder 2218)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of Liberal (Box 48:, Folder 2219-2133)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 48:, Folder 2134-2138)
    - Education, School of (Box 48:, Folder 2139-2142)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2143-2146)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2147-2150)
    - Graduate School (Box 49:, Folder 2151-2153)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2154-2157)
    - Insurance, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2158)
    - Law, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2159-2160)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2161-2164)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2165-2170)
    - Physical Education, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2171-2172)
    - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2173-2174)
    - Ratcliffe Hicks School of Agriculture (Box 49:, Folder 2175-2176)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 49:, Folder 2177-2180)
  - Curricula and Courses Committee
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 50:, Folder 2181-2183)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of Liberal (Box 50:, Folder 2184-2191)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2192-2193)
    - Education, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2194-2195)
    - Education, School of Physical (Box 50:, Folder 2196-2197)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2198-2200)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2201-2202)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2203-2204)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2205-2206)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2207-2208)
    - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 50:, Folder 2209)
    - Ratcliffe Hicks (Box 50:, Folder 2210)
  - Faculty Summer Fellowships
    - 1970 (Box 50:, Folder 2211-2214)
    - 1971 (Box 50:, Folder 2215-2218)
    - 1972 (Box 51:, Folder 2219-2222)
    - 1973 (Box 51:, Folder 2223)
  - Promotion and Tenure - Schools and Colleges
    - Agriculture (Box 51:, Folder 2224-2225)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 51:, Folder 2226)
      - Biological Sciences (Box 51:, Folder 2227-2228)
      - Chemistry and Economics (Box 51:, Folder 2229)
      - Geology (Box 51:, Folder 2230)
      - Germanic and Slavic (Box 51:, Folder 2231)
      - History (Box 51:, Folder 2232)
      - Journalism and Linguistics (Box 51:, Folder 2233)
      - Mathematics and Philosophy (Box 51:, Folder 2234)
      - Physics (Box 51:, Folder 2235)
      - Political Science (Box 51:, Folder 2236)
      - Psychology (Box 51:, Folder 2237)
      - Roman and Classical (Box 51:, Folder 2238)
      - Sociology and Anthropology (Box 51:, Folder 2239)
      - Speech and Statistics (Box 51:, Folder 2240)
    - Business Administration (and Insurance) (Box 51:, Folder 2241)
    - Education, E.O. Smith (Box 51:, Folder 2242)
    - Engineering, Fine Arts (Box 51:, Folder 2243)
    - Home Economics, Law, Physical Education, Physical Therapy, Nursing, Pharmacy, Social Work (Box 51:, Folder 2244)
    - Continuing Education, Library, Student Personnel, Auditorium, Health Services, Athletics, Public Information, Publications, Radio-TV, Honors Program (Box 51:, Folder 2245)
  - Salary Materials, 1945-1973 (Box 52)
    - College of Liberal Arts and Sciences merit increase recommendations, 1963 (Box 52:, Folder 2246-2248)
    - Salary Material (Box 52:, Folder 2249-2254)
    - Salaries and Promotions: Sp. Com. (Box 52:, Folder 2255)
    - Salary Recommendations (Box 52:, Folder 2256)
    - Salary Scale (Box 52:, Folder 2257-2260)
    - Salary Study (Box 52:, Folder 2261-2264)
    - A.A.U.P. (Box 52:, Folder 2265)
- Series VIII: Students and Student Organizations, 1940-1971
  - Aid, Student (Box 53:, Folder 2266-2268)
  - Affairs, Student (Box 53:, Folder 2269)
  - Associated Student Government (Box 53:, Folder 2270-2272)
  - Campus (Box 53:, Folder 2273)
  - Campus Disorders (Box 53:, Folder 2274)
  - Conduct and Discipline (Box 53:, Folder 2275)
  - Counseling (Box 53:, Folder 2276)
  - Drafting Committee (Box 53:, Folder 2277)
  - Enrollment Figures (Box 53:, Folder 2278)
  - Fraternities (Box 53:, Folder 2279)
  - Freshman-Sophomore basic curriculum (Box 53:, Folder 2280)
  - Graduate Students (Box 53:, Folder 2281)
  - Honors Program (Box 53:, Folder 2282)
  - Newsletter, Student (Box 53:, Folder 2283)
  - Pass/fail (Box 53:, Folder 2284)
  - Personnel, student (Box 53:, Folder 2285-2290)
  - Placement Policy (Box 54:, Folder 2291)
  - Residence Halls (Box 54:, Folder 2292)
  - Resident Counselors (Box 54:, Folder 2293-2295)
  - S.D.S. and Disorders off campus (Box 54:, Folder 2296)
  - S.D.S. and Disorders on campus (Box 54:, Folder 2297)
  - Sigma Chi (Box 54:, Folder 2298)
  - Student Senate (Box 54:, Folder 2299-2306)
  - Student Senate Constitution (Box 54:, Folder 2307)
  - Student Union (Box 54:, Folder 2308)
  - Student Union Board of Governors (Box 54:, Folder 2309-2310)
  - Student Welfare Committee (Box 54:, Folder 2311)
  - Summer Program, UConn (Box 54:, Folder 2312)
  - Summer Session (Box 54:, Folder 2313-2316)
  - University Scholars (Box 54:, Folder 2317-2320)
  - University Scholars (Box 54A, Folder 2321-2329)
  - Student files ***RESTRICTED*** (Box 55-55A)
- Series IX: Board of Trustees, 1935-1973
  - Correspondence with Board of Trustees, 1935-1962 (Box 56:, Folder 2330)
  - Trustees minutes, pp. 967-1355, 1939 October - 1946 May (Box 56:, Folder 2331-2332)
  - Trustees minutes, pp. 1356-1553, 1946 July - 1947 December (Box 56:, Folder 2333)
  - Trustees minutes, pp. 1554-1832, 1948 February - 1951 May (Box 56:, Folder 2334-2335)
  - Trustees minutes, pp. 1833-2085, 1951 September - 1953 June (Box 56:, Folder 2336-2337)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2086-2331, 1953 July - 1955 September (Box 56:, Folder 2338-2339)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2332-2495, 1955 November - 1957 November (Box 56:, Folder 2340)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2496-2614, 1958 January - 1959 March (Box 56:, Folder 2341)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2615-2788, 1959 April - 1960 July (Box 56:, Folder 2342-2343)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2789-2968, 1960 September - 1961 December (Box 56:, Folder 2344-2345)
  - Trustees material, 1961-1962 (Box 56:, Folder 2346)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.2968-3115, 1962 January - December (Box 56:, Folder 2347)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.3116-3247, 1963 January - December (Box 56:, Folder 2348-2349)
  - Trustees material, 1963 (Box 56:, Folder 2350)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.3248-3370, 1964 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2351)
  - Trustees material, 1964 (Box 57:, Folder 2352)
  - Trustees minutes, pp.3371-3520, 1965 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2353-2354)
  - Trustees material, 1965 (Box 57:, Folder 2355)
  - Trustees minutes, executive session, 1966 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2356)
  - Trustees materials, 1966 (Box 57:, Folder 2357-2358)
  - Trustees minutes, executive session, 1967 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2359)
  - Trustees material, 1967 (Box 57:, Folder 2360-2362)
  - Trustees agenda, 1968 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2363)
  - Trustees material, 1968 (Box 57:, Folder 2364)
  - Trustees agenda, 1969 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2365)
  - Trustees Minutes, executive session, 1969 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2366)
  - Trustees material, 1969 (Box 57:, Folder 2367)
  - Trustees minutes, 1969 September - 1970 July (Box 57:, Folder 2368-2369)
  - Trustees agenda, 1970 January - December (Box 57:, Folder 2370)
  - Trustees minutes, 1970 September - December (Box 57:, Folder 2371)
  - Trustees material, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 2372)
  - Trustees agenda, 1971-1972 (Box 57:, Folder 2373)
  - Trustees minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 57A, Folder 2374-2377)
  - Trustees materials, 1971 (Box 57A, Folder 2378-2379)
  - Board of Trustees: briefing (Box 57A, Folder 2380)
  - Board agenda, 1972-1973 (Box 57A, Folder 2381)
- Series X: University Senate, 1948-1974
  - Subseries A: Senate Ballots, 1962-1971
    - Senate ballots, 1962-1971 (Box 58)
  - Subseries B: Curricula and Courses Committee Records, 1955-1974
    - Senate Curricula and Courses Committee, 1955-1974
  - Subseries C: Committees, 1948-1967
    - Advisory Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2382)
    - Calendar Committee> (Box 59:, Folder 2383)
    - Civil Defense (Box 59:, Folder 2384)
    - Committees (Box 59:, Folder 2385)
    - Exhibit Committee, University (Box 59:, Folder 2386)
    - Extension Study, Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2387-2388)
    - Faculty Standards Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2389-2392)
    - Freshman-Sophomore Requirements, New (Box 59:, Folder 2393)
    - Freshman-Sophomore Requirements, Old (Box 59:, Folder 2394)
    - General Scholastic Requirements Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2395-2396)
    - Graduate School Executive Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2397-2398)
    - Growth and Development, Senate Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2399)
    - Inauguration: President Babbidge (Box 59:, Folder 2400-2401)
    - Liaison Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2402)
    - Multiple Sections Courses Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2403)
    - Powers and Functions of University Senate (Box 59:, Folder 2404)
    - Professorships Committee, University (Box 59:, Folder 2405)
    - Religion, Committee on (Box 59:, Folder 2406)
    - Senate, University: general (Box 59:, Folder 2407-2408)
    - Senate Salary Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2409)
    - Senate Scholastic Standards Committee, University (Box 59:, Folder 2410-2411)
- Series XI: Assistant Provost [Galvin Gall], 1968-1973
  - Academic Rules and Regulations (Box 60:, Folder 2412)
  - A.C.H.A. Survey - Health Services (Box 60:, Folder 2413)
  - Admissions Committee (Box 60:, Folder 2414)
  - Admissions Office (Box 60:, Folder 2415-2418)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 60:, Folder 2419)
    - A-F Subcommittee (Box 60:, Folder 2420)
    - 5-4 Subcommittee (Box 60:, Folder 2421)
  - Bison Associates (Box 60:, Folder 2422)
  - Black Studies, Center for (Box 60:, Folder 2423)
  - Branch
    - Budgets (Box 60:, Folder 2424)
    - Class Schedule (Box 60:, Folder 2425)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 60:, Folder 2426)
    - Director, Search Committee (Box 60:, Folder 2427)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 60:, Folder 2428)
      - Administration (Box 60:, Folder 2429)
      - Staff (Box 60:, Folder 2430-2432)
      - Students (Box 60:, Folder 2433-2435)
    - Proposals relating to the Branches (Box 60:, Folder 2436)
    - Proposals relating to the remodeling and/or renovations (Box 60:, Folder 2437-2438)
    - Salaries (Box 60:, Folder 2439)
    - Secretarial staffing (Box 60:, Folder 2440)
    - Southeastern Branch (Box 60:, Folder 2441-2443)
      - Administration (Box 60:, Folder 2444)
      - Plant (Box 60:, Folder 2445)
      - Staff (Box 60:, Folder 2446-2448)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 60:, Folder 2449-2451)
      - Administration (Box 60:, Folder 2452)
      - Plant (Box 60:, Folder 2453)
      - Staff (Box 60:, Folder 2454-2456)
      - Students (Box 60:, Folder 2457-2459)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 61:, Folder 2460)
      - Administration (Box 61:, Folder 2461)
      - Staff (Box 61:, Folder 2462-2464)
      - Students (Box 61:, Folder 2465-2467)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 61:, Folder 2468-2470)
      - Staff (Box 61:, Folder 2471-2473)
      - Students (Box 61:, Folder 2474-2476)
  - Bureau of Institutional Research (Box 61:, Folder 2477)
  - Bureau of Institutional Research Senior Survey (Box 61:, Folder 2478)
  - Carter, Burnham (Box 61:, Folder 2479)
  - Chapman College (Box 61:, Folder 2480)
  - CNVR Higher Education Center (Box 61:, Folder 2481)
  - Community College and Transfer (Box 61:, Folder 2482)
  - Compensating Program (Box 61:, Folder 2483)
  - Computing Courses (Box 61:, Folder 2484)
  - Connecticut Instructional Television Program (Box 61:, Folder 2485)
  - Continuing Education Services (Box 61:, Folder 2486)
  - Controller (Box 61:, Folder 2487)
  - Correspondence: Mr. Gall (Box 61:, Folder 2488)
  - Curricula Changes (Box 61:, Folder 2489)
  - Curriculum and Courses: Minimum scholastic requirements (Box 61:, Folder 2490)
  - Curriculum: The Environment and Man (Box 61:, Folder 2491)